[Music]
oh hold on a
second oh hell no he did not just text
me he working late that is weak
okay you know what working late my ass
if he don't walk through that door in
the next half an hour he may as well not
even come home tonight cuz I'm not going
to be there waiting for his cheating ass
okay you know what I'm saying me I will
be there waiting because
but he going to have to put up with a
lot of from me okay and if he think
he going to do this again he is
sely mistaken okay because my man gets
one chance okay one okay and then after
that he get one more okay and then after
that he going to get three
strikes then you're out okay and if I
ever find out that my man was messing
around on me he better get as far away
from me as he possibly can because he do
not want to get what I'm going to give
to him okay I got my real
estate license okay but if and when he
does come home that's fine okay cuz he
can go out and get all turned up with
these little side hoes and whatnot cuz
you know what he always going to
come home all right okay I'm the queen
bee and he always going to come home to
me you know what okay you know but you
know I don't even care okay but I'll
tell you what happen if you do come home
he ain't going to be pulling anything
that in my house okay yeah he can
come to the house if he wants to but he
ain't never going to do that when I'm
home okay you know what even if I'm home
it's
fine okay you know what I'm talking
about okay cuz I don't give a good
goddamn that's what I'm talking about
but he ain't going to bring that
into my bedroom I'll tell you that much
right now okay cuz ain't no tripling ass
going to wake me up while he's
cheating on me in my bed again okay and
I told him I looked him right in the
face I said this is the fifth and last
time
okay I couldn't have said it better
myself go you right okay you just been
spouting words of wisdom all evening I
ain't listening to a damn thing you
say I don't even know what the hell I
was thinking girl you right the second
that that man walks through that door
I'm going dump his ass
oh okay okay okay oh my gosh speak it a
[Music]
devil
oh
okay
okay I know
need